<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="help_supply1">Welcome to Androminion, an unofficial Android implementation of the award-winning strategy card game Dominion, by Donald X. Vaccarino and published by Rio Grande Games.</string>
	<string name="help_supply2">If you don\'t know how to play Dominion, read the How to Play section for a summary.</string>
	<string name="help_supply3">This is the Supply. The Supply consists of cards available to buy during the game.
	    &lt;p&gt;Basic Treasure cards are on top with Curse and basic Victory cards under. Beneath those are the Kingdom cards, which change every game. Any landscape and non-Supply cards will be shown under the Supply.&lt;/p&gt;</string>
	<string name="help_supply4">&lt;p&gt;The cost of each card is in the yellow circle to the left of its name (red circles show Debt costs and blue circles are costs with potion).&lt;/p&gt; 
	    &lt;p&gt;Beneath is the remaining count of cards in that pile.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;Any tokens on piles will be shown on the right.&lt;/p&gt; 
		&lt;p&gt;You can long-press on any card to see its full details.&lt;/p&gt;</string>

	<string name="help_turn1">This is the turn view. Here you can see stats for each player and info about the current turn.</string>
	<string name="help_turn2">The current turn\'s player is highlighted, and players are listed in turn order.</string>
	<string name="help_turn3">If enabled, the numbers under players\' names show the number of cards in their deck, hand, total cards and Victory points.</string>
	<string name="help_turn4">&lt;p&gt;Any tokens a player has are shown to the right of their name.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;Long-press a player for full details.&lt;/p&gt;</string>
	<string name="help_turn5">A message with the currently requested input is shown above the players. The current number of actions, buys, and coins are shown at the top of the screen.</string>

	<string name="help_hand1">This first column shows the cards in your hand. Only you can see them. </string>
	<string name="help_hand2">The second column shows the cards that are in play. This is visible to all. Grayed-out cards here were played for this turn but are not currently in play.</string>
	<string name="help_hand3">If you have cards on mats or other set-aside areas, swipe the view left to show them. The trash is shown in the far right column and is visible to all.</string>
	<string name="help_hand4">If any of these columns gets too long, you may need to drag the view up or down to see everything.</string>
	<string name="help_hand5">Again, long-press any card to show details.</string>
	
	<string name="help_log1">Finally, a history of the game is displayed in the scrollable game log at the bottom of your screen.
		&lt;p&gt;You can always bring up this help again through the menu while a game is running.&lt;/p&gt;</string>

	<string name="help_end">Good luck, and enjoy the game!</string>

	<string name="help_next">Next page</string>
	<string name="help_quit">Exit help</string>
</resources>
