<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="help_supply1">Welcome to Androminion, an Android implementation of the award winning strategy card game Dominion, by Donald X. Vaccarino and published by Rio Grande Games. </string>
	<string name="help_supply2">If you are unfamiliar with how to play Dominion, it is highly recommended to read the official rules or the Wikipedia entry first.  Links can be found at \n\t http://android.mehtank.com. </string>
	<string name="help_supply3">This is the card supply.  Here you can see all of the cards available for purchase in this game.
		\n\nTo find out more information about a card, simply long-press on the card to bring up a dialog with its details.</string>
	<string name="help_supply4">Each card lists its cost in the yellow circle on the left of the card and the remaining quantity under the card name.
		\n\nIf Embargo is in play, the number of embargo tokens on a supply pile will be displayed in a black circle on the right of the card. </string>

	<string name="help_turn1">This is the turn view.  Here you can see the stats about each player along with information about the current turn. </string>
	<string name="help_turn2">The current turn\'s player is highlighted, and the players are listed in turn order.</string>
	<string name="help_turn3">The numbers under the players\' names indicate the number of cards in their draw pile, hand, and deck (including any mats), respectively. </string>
	<string name="help_turn4">If Pirate Ships are in play, the number of pirate ship tokens is displayed in a red circle to the right of the player\'s name. </string>
	<string name="help_turn5">The current number of actions, buys, and money is listed at the bottom, along with a message about what input is being requested. </string>

	<string name="help_hand1">The first column shows the cards that are currently in your hand.  This is only visible to you. </string>
	<string name="help_hand2">The second column shows the cards that have been played in the current turn.  This is visible to everyone. </string>
	<string name="help_hand3">If you have cards in your Native Village or Island, swipe the view to the left to view the contents of those mats. </string>
	<string name="help_hand4">If any of these columns gets too big, you may need to drag the view up or down to see all the cards. </string>
	<string name="help_hand5">Again, you can long-press any card to bring up further details. </string>
	
	<string name="help_log1">Finally, a history of the game is displayed in the scrollable game log at the bottom of your screen.
		\n\nYou can always bring up this help again through the menu while a game is running.</string>

	<string name="help_end">Good luck, and enjoy the game! \n\n\n\t\t\t-:ankur</string>

	<string name="help_next">Next page</string>
	<string name="help_quit">Exit help</string>
</resources>
